A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness House drawings, SG 2 FA247
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Third Floor, 1906-1983; 5
  - Building-Floor Plans, 5.1
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, 1908 April 7; Order Number 589 (Folder 127)
      (Not a Complete Drawing)...Fireplace Chamber No. 1, 1-@ 31 3/4"x31 7/8", (6 Other Pieces from Original Drawing), 2-14 1/2"x9 3/4", 3-13"x7 1/2", 4-12 1/2"x4 7/8", Others are small, Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, 1908 March 20; 719 (Office Copy) (Folder 128)
      North Elevation Chamber No. 1, 21 3/4"x14 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A (Hale and Rogers)
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, 1908 March 20; 720 (Office Copy) (Folder 128)
      Plan of Chamber No. 1 .Written on the Back in Pencil, Chamber No. 1 3rd Fl., 21 1/8"x25", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A (Hale and Rogers)
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, undated; 721 (Office Copy) (Folder 128)
      East Elevation Chamber No. 1, 24 1/4"x14 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A (Hale and Rogers)
      Received 4/3/1908 Charles T. Wills, 4/8/1908 Haleand Rogers
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, 1966 September 1; 722 (Office Copy) (Folder 128)
      West Elevation Chamber No. 1, 25 3/8"x14 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A (Hale and Rogers)
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, undated; 722A (Office Copy) (Folder 128)
      South Elevation Chamber No. 1, 18 7/8"x14 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A (Hale and Rogers)
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, 1908 March 26; 759 (Office Copy) (Folder 128)
      West Elevation Chamber No. 1, Alterations to Fireplace, 21 1/4"x15 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, undated; 902 (Office Copy) (Folder 129)
      Bathroom No. 1, Third Floor, 26 1/2"x26 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Chas T Wills, Inc. Builders, Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co., Carrara Glass Department, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, undated; 1078 (Office Copy) (Folder 129)
      Plan of Chamber No. 1, 22 7/8"x25 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, undated; 1079 (Office Copy) (Folder 129)
      East Elevation, Chamber No. 1, #1-24 5/8"x14 1 /2", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-24 5/8"x14 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, undated; 1080 (Office Copy) (Folder 130)
      West Elevation, Chamber No. 1, # 1-26x15 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-25 7/8"x15", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, undated; 1081 (Office Copy) (Folder 130)
      North Elevation, Chamber No. 1, # 1-21 5/8"x14 15/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios, #2-21 3/4"x14 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, undated; 1082 (Office Copy) (Folder 130)
      South Elevation, Chamber No. 1, # 1-21 3/8"x16", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios, # 2-21 1/2"x16", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, undated; 1088 (Office Copy) (Folder 131)
      Full Size Details, Chamber No. 1, Plan of Mantle at Base, Door Trim, # 1-22 1/2"x41 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Tiffany Chamber No. 1, 21 1/2"x39", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A, (Tiffany Studios)
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, 1908 August 12; 1131 (Folder 132)
      ...Closets off Chamber No. 1. ...se in Closets of Chamber.. (pieces are missing and torn), @ 36"x48 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, 1908 April 21; Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 31 (Folder 133)
      Plan and Detail of Chamber No. 1, Full Scale Plan of Base at Mantle, Full Scale Section of Base, Full Scale Detail of Plinth, Written on the Back in Pencil, Marble Base, Chamber No. 1, 28 1/4"x20", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, undated (Folder 133)
      Plan of Chamber No. 1, 20 1/2"x25 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, 1908 May 14 (Folder 133)
      Section Thru Radiator Enclosure, Bathroom No. 1, Third Floor, Written on the Back in Pencil, Section Thru Radiator Enclosure, Bathroom No.1, Third Floor, 13"x10 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, G.A. Suter and Co.
    - Chamber No. 1-Bathroom No. 1, undated (Folder 133)
      Full Size Details Chamber # 1, Plan of Mantle at Base, Full Detail of Cornice Chamber # 1, Full Size Detail of Wainscoting, Full Size Detail of Corner Chamber # 1, Trim, Written on the Back in Pencil, Tiffany's Drawings Chamber No. 1 3rd..., 15 7/8"x31 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - Hall/Stair Hall, 1908 February 5; 356 NY 33 (Folder 134)
      Plan of Third Floor Stair Hall, Elevation, Detailed Note on the Right Side, #1-29 3/4"x15 1/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-29 7/8"x15", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Hall/Stair Hall, 1908 August 28; 399-10 NY 33 (Folder 134)
      (No Title) East Corridor, Third Story {Cut Jambs to these Lines}, # 1-14 7/8"x14 1/2", Tracing Paper, # 2-15"x14 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Hall/Stair Hall, 1908 May 4; 911 (Office Copy), Drawing Number 41 (Folder 135)
      Plan and Elevations of Stairs Third to Fourth Floors, Plan, Section A-A, Section B-B, Section C-C, Section D-D, Developed Elevation, 2 Pieces of Paper are Glued Together, 50 1/4"x28 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Hall/Stair Hall, 1908 April 30; 913 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 37 (Folder 134)
      Plan and Elevation of Stair Hall, Third Floor,, # 1-29"x22 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2- (No Title), Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Drawing No. 37, Plan and Elevation of Stair Hall, Third Floor, 29"x16 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Hall/Stair Hall, undated; 1076 (Office Copy) (Folder 136)
      Plan of the Third Floor, 25 3/8"x16", Tracing Paper, Architects, N/A (Hale and Rogers)
    - Hall/Stair Hall, 1908 July 17; 1094 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 65 (Folder 136)
      Plan of Marble Base and Plinth Blocks West Corridor, Third Floor, 24 1/2"x9 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Hall/Stair Hall, 1908 July 23; 1097 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 67 (Folder 136)
      Plan of Marble Base and Plinth Blocks, East Corridor, Third Floor, # 1-24 1/8"x10 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Marble Base, 3 Floor East Corridor, 24 1/4"x10 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Hall/Stair Hall, 1908 April 27; Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 35 (Folder 136)
      Full Scale Section of Wainscot in 3rd and 4th Fl Stair Halls, Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Drawing, No. 35, FRS. Sections of Wainscot in 3rd and 4th Fl. Stair-Halls, 14 1/4"x27 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Hall/Stair Hall, undated (Folder 136)
      Stairs to Fourth Floor (Written on the Back in Pencil), 30 1/2"x24 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A (Possibly Torn Off)
  - HVAC, 5.2
    - HVAC, 1982 October 5; AC-3, Job Number 26-82 (Folder 137)
      Proposed Air Conditioning System, Third Floor (Commonwealth Fund), 36 1/2"x20", Sepia Tone, Architects, P and O Air Control Co., Inc.
    - HVAC, 1983 May 24; M-4 (Folder 138)
      Alterations to HVAC System, Third Floor Plan and Fourth Floor Plan-HVAC and Electric, Electrical Notes, Notes on the Right Side, 49 1/4"x30 1/4, Paper, Architects, Stramandinoli, Mellusi and Khlyavich
    - HVAC, 1907 April 9 (Folder 137)
      Third Story Plan, Notes on the Bottom, It's a Copy, Paper Size-24"x18 1/4", Image Size-23 1/4"x12 1/2", Paper, Architects, N/A
  - Plumbing, 5.3
    - Plumbing, 1978 June 5; 049-01, A-1 (Folder 139)
      Proposed Alterations Third Floor, Plot Plan, Plumbing Riser and Men's Toilet, Diagram of Women's Toilet, (Commonwealth Fund) 36 1/2"x19 1/8", Paper, Architects, Francis Day Rogers
    - Plumbing, 1907 April 15; 1368 (Folder 139)
      Plumbing Plans, Third Story Plan, # 1-36 1/2"x15 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Is a Copy, Paper Size-24"x18 1/4", Image Size, 20 1/2"x8 3/4", Paper, Architects, Albert L. Webster, Civil and Sanitary Engineer
  - Electrical, 5.4
    - Electrical, 1950 December 28-1953 February 3; Job Number 421, Drawing Number 3 (Folder 140, Folder 141)
      Alteration to One East 75th St NYC for the Commonwealth Fund, Third Floor Plan and Fourth Floor Plan, Trims Types and Door Types, Door Schedules, # 1-Written on the Back in Pencil, Telephone, 42 1/8"x26", Diazo Blue Print, Alterations: 1/25/1951-Exits, Doors and Stairs Revised, 4/10/1951-General Owner Requests-DV Removed, 4/23/1951-Plumbing, Door Schedule and General Notes Added, 5/16/1951-Owner Requests, 5/22/1951-Drink Fountain Located 4th Floor-Door Frames Retained 3-13, # 2-Electrical (Stamped), 42"x26", Paper, # 3-Has the Architects Pencil Notations, Electrical (Stamped), 42 3/4"x26 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 4-No Electrical Stamp, 41 5/8"x26 1/4", Diazo Blue Print.
      #1-12/28/1950 #2-Revised 6/26/1951, Received 2/3/1953 Rogers and Butler #3-Revised 6/26/1951, Received 7/3/1951 Rogers and Butler #4-Revised 1/25/1951, 4/10/1951, 4/13/1951
    - Electrical, 1951 June 26-1953 February 2; 84 (Folder 140, Folder 141)
      #5-Electrical (Stamped), Small Piece of Paper Taped to the Bottom Left Corner, 3rd Floor-East Corridor Floor Lamp, 3rd Floor West Corridor Table Lamp, First Floor Panel Box Fuse # 4 Exit Lights, Note: Light in above ONLY WHEN FUSE # 4 is ON, 2/6/69, 42"x26", Diazo Blue Print, # 6-Electrical (Stamped), 42"x26", Diazo Blue Print, # 7-Electrical-Revised: 6/26/1951-3rd Floor Outlets Added in Space Nos. 3-7, 3-8, 3-10, 4th Floor Outlets Added or Omitted in Space No. 4-3, 4-11, 2/2/1953-Revised as per Contractors Marked Up Drawings,43 7/8"x27 7/8", Linen (Blue), # 8-Exits-Doors and Stairs Revised, 1/25/1951, 42"x26", Paper, Architects, # 1-Rogers and Butler, # 2-Rogers and Butler, Clifton E. Smith and Edward B. Silverman, Consulting Electrical Engineers, # 3-4-Rogers and Butler, # 5-7-Rogers and Butler, Clifton E. Smith and Edward B. Silverman, Consulting Electrical Engineers, # 8-Rogers and Butler.
      #5-Revised 6/26/1951, 2/2/1953 #6-Revised 6/26/1951 #7-Revised 6/26/1951, 2/2/1953 #8-Revised 1/25/1951
      #5-Received 2/3/1953 Rogers and Butler #6-Received 7/3/1951 Rogers and Butler
    - Electrical, 1981 October-November; Order Number 2047, 1824/3 (Folder 141)
      Panel -A- 3rd Floor and Panel -A- 4th Floor, 21 1/4"x35", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, H. Krantz Manufacturing Co.
- Fourth Floor, 1906-1984; 6
  - Building-Floor Plans, 6.1
    - Building-Floor Plans, 1906 November 8; 5 NY 33 (Folder 142)
      Fourth Floor Plan, 42"x22", Linen, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Building-Floor Plans, 1907 April 29; 111 NY 33 (Folder 142)
      Fourth Floor Framing Plan, Fifth Floor Framing Plan, Section Through Curb Framing of Skylight, Typical Section Through Main Cornice, Plan of Steel Brackets, # 1-42"x32 1/4", Linen, # 2-42"x32", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Building-Floor Plans, 1984 September 19; Revised 1984 November 10; 1984 December 9 (Folder 142)
      Milbank Fund, Plan, Demolition and Construction, 36 1/8"x24", Paper, Architects, N/A
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, 1907 October 1; 306 NY 33 (Folder 143)
      Scale Details of Lintels Over Two Door Openings of Chamber No. 2, Plan, Section Through Lintel Over Doors, 15 3/4"x18 7/8", Linen, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, 1908 February 1; 360 NY 33 (Folder 143)
      Details of Bathroom No. 2 in Fourth Story, Plan, North Elevation, South Elevation, East Elevation, West Elevation, # 1-34 1/8"x22 7/8", Linen, # 2-22 7/8"x34 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, 1908 February 5; 377 NY 33 (Folder 143)
      Plan of Chamber No. 2, # 1-23 3/8"x19 3/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-23 3/8"x19 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, 1908 February 5; 378 NY 33 (Folder 144)
      Chamber No. 2, South Elevation, General Note on the Right Side, # 1-Hand Written Note Across the Top of the Drawing Which Has Been Erased, 23 3/8"x17", Tracing Paper, # 2-23 1/2"x16 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, 1908 February 5; 379 NY 33 (Folder 144)
      Chamber No. 2, East Elevation, # 1-23 1/4"x17", Tracing Paper, # 2-23 1/4"x16 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, 1908 February 5; 380 NY 33 (Folder 145)
      Chamber No. 2, North Elevation, # 1-23 1/2"x16 7/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-23 3/8"x16 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, 1908 April 6; Order Number 589 (Folder 146)
      (Not a Complete Drawing)...At Doorway Chamber No. 2, Written on the Back in Pencil, F.S.D. of Doorway Chamber...Fourth FI...[oor], @ 29 3/4"x46 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, 1908 March 20; 706 (Office Copy) (Folder 145)
      East Elevation of Chamber No. 2, 22"x14", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, 1908 March 20 and undated; 707 (Office Copy) (Folder 145)
      Chamber No. 2, #1-19 1/2"x23", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A (Hale and Rogers), # 2-19"x21 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A
      #1-3/20/1908 #2-undated
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, 1908 March 20; 708 (Office Copy) (Folder 147)
      North Elevation Chamber No. 2, 19 3/8"x14 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A (Hale and Rogers)
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, 1908 March 20; 709 (Office Copy) (Folder 147)
      West Elevation of Chamber No. 2, South Elevation Similar, 21 1/4"x13 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A (Hale and Rogers)
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, undated; 1083 (Office Copy) (Folder 147)
      Plan of Chamber No. 2, Full Scale Detail in Three Corners, Full Size Detail of Northeast Corner, # 1-25 1/4"x27 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Chamber No. 2, 23 1/2"x27 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, undated; 1084 (Office Copy) (Folder 147)
      North Elevation, Chamber No. 2, 19 3/8"x13, # 1-1/4" Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios, # 2-17 1/8"x13 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A, (Tiffany Studios)
      #1-Received 7/11/1908 Hale and Rogers #2-Received 4/22/1908 Charles T. Wills
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, undated; 1085 (Office Copy) (Folder 148)
      East Elevation, Chamber No. 2, # 1-22 1/2"x13", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Tiffany Chamber No. 2, 20 1/4"x12 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, undated; 1086 (Office Copy) (Folder 148)
      South Elevation, Chamber No. 2, # 1-24 1/8"x14" Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios, # 2-18 1/8"x13", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A, (Tiffany Studios)
      Received 7/11/1908 Hale and Rogers #2-undated, Received 4/22/1908 Charles T. Wills
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, undated; 1087 (Office Copy) (Folder 148)
      Mantel, Chamber No. 2, 13 5/8"x19", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, 1908 July 27-31; 1108 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 77 (Folder 149)
      Plan and Elevation of Mantle Facing and Hearth in Chamber No. 2, Full Scale Section Thro' Mantel and Facing, # 1-34 1/8"x11 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Plan and Elevation of Chamber No. 2, 32"x11 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      #1-7/27/1908 #2-7/27/1908, Revised 7/31/1908
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, 1908 March 31; Revised 1908 April 4; 1908 April 16; 1908 May 26; Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 17 (Folder 149)
      Plan and Elevation of Bathroom No. 2, Fourth Floor, Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Details of Bathroom-2-Fourth Floor, Latest Draw, {Octagonal Shape} 25 1/8"x25 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co., Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, undated (Folder 149)
      West Elevation, Chamber No. 2, 19 7/8"x13", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A, (Tiffany Studios)
      Received 4/22/1908 Charles T. Wills
    - Chamber No. 2-Bathroom No. 2, undated (Folder 149)
      Section of Door Jamb Between Chamber No. 2 and Bathroom No. 2,, Written on the Back in Pencil, Tiffany's F.S.D. Showing Section of Door Jamb Bet. Chamber 2 and Bathroom 2, Fourth Floor, 10 5/8"x12 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Tiffany Studios
    - Chamber No. 3-Bathroom No. 3, 1907 December 11; 314 NY 33 (Folder 150)
      Scale and Full Size Details of Iron Smoke Flues in Bathroom No. 3, Fourth Story, Plan of Iron Door Looking Up, Section Looking North, Section Looking East at "X-X", Full Scale Detail of Thimble A, B-C-D Similar, Elevation Looking North, Plan of Bathroom # 3, Full Scale Detail of Joint Between Terra-Cotta and Inclined Smoke Flues, Section Thro "R-R" Looking East, 26 1/2"x37 3/8", Linen, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 3-Bathroom No. 3, 1908 February 1; 361 NY 33 (Folder 150)
      Details of Bathroom No. 3, Fourth Story, Plan, North Elevation, South Elevation, East Elevation, West Elevation, # 1-34 1/8"x22 1/4", Linen, # 2-22 1/2"x34 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 3-Bathroom No. 3, 1908 February 5; 381 NY 33 (Folder 150)
      Chamber No. 3 Plan, Chamber No. 4 Plan, General Note on the Left Side, # 1-2 Pieces of Paper Glued Together, 35 1/8"x17 1/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-35 1/2"x17 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 3-Bathroom No. 3, 1981 November 13; 382 NY 33 (Folder 150)
      Chamber No. 3, South Elevation, West Elevation, # 1- (2 Pieces of Paper Glued Together), 32 1/2"x13 1/2", Tracing Paper, # 2-33"x13 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 3-Bathroom No. 3, 1908 February 5; 383 NY 33 (Folder 151)
      Chamber No. 3, North Elevation, East Elevation, # 1-4 Pieces of Paper Glued Together (the center, the left edge, and the top right corner), 31 3/8"x13 5/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-31 1/2"x13 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 3-Bathroom No. 3, 1908 May 26; Revised 1908 June 6; 952 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing 51 (Folder 151)
      Plan and Elevation of Radiator Enclosure, Full Scale Section Thro' Sill, Bathroom No. 3, 4th Floor, # 1-22 3/4"x12", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Drawing of Radiator Enclosure-Bathroom 3 Fourth Floor, 22"x12", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Chamber No. 3-Bathroom No. 3, 1908 May 22; 957 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 47 (Folder 151)
      Plan of Base in Chamber No. 3, Fourth Floor, Full Size Details of Plinths, Section of the Base, # 1-27 5/8"x21 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Detail of Marble Base in Chamber No. 3, 4th Floor, 28 1/8"x22 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Chamber No. 4-Bathroom No. 4, 1908 February 1; 362 NY 33 (Folder 152)
      Details of Bathroom No. 4, Fourth Story, Plan, East Elevation, North Elevation, Details of Bathroom No. 5, Fourth Story, Plan, North Elevation, East Elevation, # 1-34"x22 3/4", Linen, # 2-22 3/4"x34 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 4-Bathroom No. 4, 1908 February 5; 384 NY 33 (Folder 152)
      Chamber No. 4, South Elevation, West Elevation, # 1-2 Pieces of Paper Glued Together, 30 3/8"x16 3/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-30 5/8"x16 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 4-Bathroom No. 4, 1908 February 5; 385 NY 33 (Folder 152)
      Chamber No. 4, East Elevation, North Elevation, General Note on the Top Right, #1-2 Pieces of Paper Glued Together in the Center, 29 3/8"x17 1/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-Paper Size-29 1/2"x17 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 4-Bathroom No. 4, 1908 May 25; Revised 1908 June 6; 950 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing 49 (Folder 152)
      Plan and Elevation of Bathroom No. 4, 4th Floor, #119 3/4"x17 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Drawing of Bathroom 4-Fourth Floor, 19 1/4"x18", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Chamber No. 4-Bathroom No. 4, 1908 May 22; 956 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 46 (Folder 153)
      Plan of Base in Chamber No. 4, Fourth Floor, Section of Base, # 1-25 1/4"x17 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Detail of Marble Base in Chamber No. 4, Fourth Floor (Writing was cut off), 24 7/8"x17 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Chamber No. 4-Bathroom No. 4, 1908 May 23; Revised 1908 June 6; Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 48 (Folder 153)
      Section of Base and Trim in Bathrooms No. 4 and 5, Fourth Floor, Section of Base Under Radiator Enclosure, Elevation, #1-16 3/4"x19 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's ...ing Show...Section...Base an...Trim In B...Rooms 4..Fourth Fl...{writing is cut off due to the edge being cut}, 16 7/8"x26 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Chamber No. 5-Bathroom No. 5, 1908 February 5; 386 NY 33 (Folder 154)
      Plan of Chamber No. 5, Plan of Chamber No. 6, General Note on the Right Side, # 1-30 1/8"x17 3/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-30"x17 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 5-Bathroom No. 5, 1908 February 5; 387 NY 33 (Folder 154)
      Chamber No. 5, North Elevation, South Elevation, # 1-2 Pieces of Paper Glued Together, 30 1/4"x14 7/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-30 1/4"x15 7/8", Diazo Blue Print. Architects. Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 5-Bathroom No. 5, 1908 February 5; 388 NY 33 (Folder 154)
      Chamber No. 5, West Elevation, East Elevation, # 1-2 Pieces of Paper Glued Together, 30 1/4"x14 7/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-30 1/4"x14 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 5-Bathroom No. 5, 1908 May 26-June 6; 951 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 50 (Folder 155)
      Plan and Elevation of Bathroom No. 5, Fourth Floor, #1-14 1/8"x18 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Drawing of Bathroom, 5, Fourth Floor, 14 1/8"x18 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      #1-5/26/1908 #2-5/26/1908, Revised 6/6/1908
    - Chamber No. 5-Bathroom No. 5, 1908 June 28; 1037 (Office Copy), Drawing Number 61 (Folder 155)
      Details of Facing and Hearths for Chamber No. 5 and No. 6, Chamber No. 5 Plan, Elevation, Full Scale Plan, Chamber No. 6, Plan, Elevation, # 1-34"17 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitels Detail of Facings and Hearth for Chamber No. 5 and 6, Fourth Floor, 34 1/8"x@ 19", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Chamber No. 5-Bathroom No. 5, undated; No P #, 723 (Probably P-8) (Folder 156)
      Plan of Chamber No. 5, Written on the Back in Pencil, P andS's Drawings Chamber No. 5-4th Floor (Some of the writing is cut off), 18 1/4"x@ 20 1/2" (edges are torn and uneven), Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
    - Chamber No. 5-Bathroom No. 5, undated; P-9, 724 (Folder 156)
      South Elevation of Chamber No. 5, 15 3/8"x17 1/8", Paper, Architects, N/A, (Probably Pottier and Stymus Co.)
    - Chamber No. 5-Bathroom No. 5, undated; P-10, 725 (Folder 156)